Hello ladies, look what I just received
Foreo Luna 4
Foreo Bird 2
Foreo Bird 2 for eyes and lips
and then all of their conductive serums
What I'm going to start trying today
Oh my goodness, so many really cool things.
I'll show you as I start the treatment.
when I download the app
because honestly, I'm very curious
to get to know all these products
and it comes with the super complete kit
I’ve also bought this little box.
to be able to save all those things there
so nothing
I'm going to do unboxings of everything.
I'm going to try it and let you know my impressions.
because I see that there are a lot of questions and doubts
So I'm going to start from scratch.
I'm going to leave you a comment.
I'm going to explain everything to you.
How to use it and how is it going for me
so far